Previously on
The Big Bang Theory:
섹스 도중에 어떻게
그런 말을 할 수 있어?
Who says something like that
right in the middle of sex?!
I don't know.
너무 뜨거운 순간이어서
It was the heat of the moment!
'그래, 바로 그렇게'가 아니라?
No, the heat of the moment is
"Ooh, yeah, just like that."
'나랑 결혼해줄래?'
Not, "Will you marry me?"
우주 정거장에
망원경을 설치하고 싶대
NASA really wants my telescope
up on the Space Station,
더 일찍 떠나게 됐어
so they're putting me
on an earlier launch.
언제?
When?
다음 주 금요일
A week from Friday.
다음 주 일요일이 결혼식인데
What? We're getting
married that Sunday.
그러네
You're right.
못 가겠다
I can't go to space.
결혼해야 되잖아
I have to get married.
누구나 다 이해할 거야
No one can say
that's not a good reason.
못 간다고 할게
I'll call them back.
결혼식은 돌아올
때까지 미루자
We'll have the wedding
when you get back.
아버님께서 싫어할게 뻔해
Your dad's going
to be furious.
허락하시지 않을걸
There's no way
he's going to let us
어쩔 수 없다
(chuckles) postpone this
wedding. Well, we tried.
내가 설득해볼게
I'll talk to him.
내가 부탁하면 될 거야
He won't say no
to his little girl.
아니, 내가 얘기할게
No! I, uh,
I should talk to him.
남자 대 남자로
Man to man.
솔직히 말씀드릴게요
All right, look,
I'm going to level with you.
비행이 너무 두려워요
I'm terrified about
going into space.
못 돌아오면 어쩌죠?
You know, what if
I don't make it back?
잘 될 거야
It's going to be okay, son.
정말 그렇게 생각하세요?
You really think so?
물론이지
Of course.
베르나데트처럼 이쁜 아이는
A pretty girl
like Bernadette,
새로운 남자가 생길 거야
she'll find a new guy.
(man speaking Russian)
(speaking Russian)
어이, 마이크
Hey, Mike?
Yeah...
생각이 바뀌었어,
이런거 하고 싶지 않아
I changed my mind.
I don't want to do this.
재밌네
Good one.
응, 내가 좀 재밌지
Yeah, I'm a funny guy.
비행 내내 울 계획인데
그것도 웃기겠지
I also have a hysterical bit
planned for later
where I pretend to cry
through the whole launch.
(both laughing)
(laughs)
(all laughing)
NASA 채널이 몇이지?
Sheldon, what channel
is NASA TV?
289, 288번 게임쇼 네트워크랑
290번 디즈니 사이야
289, right between
the Game Show Network at 288
and the East coast feed of the
Disney Channel on 290.
기억력이 너무 섹시해
I love his eidetic
memory, it's so sexy.
쉘든, 프링글스 재료가
어떻게 되지?
Sheldon, what are the
ingredients in Pringles?
말린감자, 식물성유지
Dried potatoes, vegetable oil,
옥수수가루, 밀전분
corn flower, wheat starch,
말토덱스트린, 정제소금
maltodextrin, salt,
그리고 내가 제일
좋아하는 균일성
and my favorite ingredient
of all, uniformity.
자궁이 떨리지 않니?
The uterus quivers,
does it not?
하워드가 카자흐스탄에서
라이브로 나온다
There's Howard's rocket,
live from Kazakhstan.
너무 긴장돼
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
못 보겠어
I don't think I can watch.
난 스트레스 받아서
나흘 동안 음식으로 풀었어
You're nervous? I've been
stress-eating for four days.
이것 좀 봐
Look at me.
뚱뚱할 때 입는 바지야
I'm wearing my fat pants.
30분 내에
Remarkable.
In just under a half hour,
하워드의 엉덩이 밑으로
200 metric tons
of fuel will
200 메트릭톤 연료가
통제 폭파될 거야
ignite in a
controlled explosion
right beneath
Howard's keister.
이 모든 걸 책임지는 나라는
And all from a country whose
entire contribution
국제 경제에 테트리스랑
다문화가정을 공급했어
to the global economy, has been
Tetris and mail-order brides.
프링글스 내놔
Give me those
damn Pringles.
(speaking Russian)
MAN (over radio):
Da.
카운트다운 곧 들어간다
Okay, we're in
the final countdown.
그쪽은 괜찮아?
How you doing over there?
응, 좋아
Good! Good!
뭐 좀 물어볼게
Oh, quick question,
I missed it in the briefing.
오줌 주머니가 얼마나 크지?
How much urine
do these suits hold?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x24
The Countdown Reflection
Original Air Date on May 10, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
후르트룹스,
거기
팬 스위치 좀 눌러봐
Hey, Froot Loops, want
to hit your fan switch?
Check.
게이 머리 스타일 때문에
후르트룹스라고 불려?
He calls you Froot Loops because
of your very gay haircut?
아니, 엄마랑 사는데
No, it's...
'cause I live with my mom
씨리얼을 해주시거든
and she makes me Froot Loops.
(chuckles)
게이라고 하는게
더 받아들이기 쉬워
Go with gay story, people
are more accepting of that.
Actually,
후르트룹스는 최근에
여자랑 결혼했어
Froot Loops just got
married to a girl.
축하해
Congratulations.
고마워, 비행 전에 끝냈어
Thanks, we decided to do it
before the launch.
룹스 부인이랑
결혼식은 잘 치뤘나?
You and Mrs. Loops
have a big wedding?
꼭 그런건 아냐,
괜찮다면 조용히 있고 싶어
Not exactly.
Listen, if you don't mind,
수다 떨 기분이 아니네
I'm not really up for chatting.
눈 앞에 스쳐지나가는
인생을 감상하고 있을게
I'm just going to
sit here quietly
and let my life
flash before my eyes.
(big sigh)
너무 빨리 지나갔네
다시 해볼게
That went really quick.
Let me try it again.
눈 감고 손 내밀어
Close your eyes.
Put out your hand.
특별한 걸 준비했어
I got you something special.
하워드, 이번엔 안 속아
Come on, Howard.
I'm not falling for that again.
No, here...
Oh, Howie.
별 목걸이네
A little star.
너무 이쁘다
It's beautiful.
(chuckles)
걸어줘
Put it on me.
한번만 해보고 돌려줘
Okay, but I'm going to have
to get it back for you
국제우주정거장에
가져갈 생각이야
so I can take it to the
International Space Station.
내가 돌아오면
That way, when I come home,
우주에서 따온
별이 될 거야
you will have a star
that was actually in space.
Oh... my God.
다른 남자들이 준
선물은 비교도 안돼
Take that, every guy who's ever
bought you anything. (chuckles)
내 인생 최고의 선물이야
This is the most amazing
gift I've ever gotten.
정말?
그렇게 좋으면...
Really? Well, if you like it
that much,
눈 감고 손 내밀어
then close your eyes
and put out your hand.
(both chuckle)
마트에서 간식 사오려는데
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I'm going to the
supermarket to buy
후르트룹스도 사올까?
snacks for your trip!
Do you want me to
get those little boxes
of Froot Loops you like?!
후르트룹스 먹으면
다른 사람들이 놀려요
No! When I eat Froot Loops,
the other astronauts
make fun of me!
하워드, 결혼식을
미루고 싶지 않아
Howard, I don't want
to wait until
you're back to get married.
뭐?
What?
네가 로켓에 타기
전에 하고 싶어
I want to be
married to you
before you get
in that rocket.
이틀 후면 떠나는데
But I'm leaving in two days.
애플잭스는 어때?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
What about Apple Jacks?!
씨리얼은 필요 없어요
I don't need
to take cereal!
러시아에서 아침을
차려줄 거 같냐?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: What kind of
breakfast do you think
they're going to
give you in Russia?!
블린츠를 발명했잖아요,
걱정 마세요
They invented blintzes!
I'll be fine!
뉴저지에 있는
백열 전구를 발명했는데
MRS. WOLOWITZ: They invented
the lightbulb in New Jersey!
그렇다고 공짜로
나눠주는 건 아니지
It doesn't mean they hand them
out to you when you go!
친구들만 불러서
간단한 식을 올리고
We'll have a quick little
ceremony with just our friends,
피로연은 돌아오면 하자
and we'll still have
the big reception
with everyone when
you get back.
Wow. (chuckles)
그래, 결혼하자
Okay. Let's get married.
(chuckles)
혹시 모르니까 섬유질 많은
올브랜으로 사올게
MRS. WOLOWITZ: You know what,
I'll buy you All-Bran
in case you get
stopped up in outer space.
시청에 가서
혼인신고를 하기로 했어
So anyway, we decided to go down
to City Hall this afternoon
결혼부터 하고 피로연은
하워드가 돌아오면 할거야
get married, and then have the
reception when Howard gets back.
잘됐다
Great!
That's so good!
갑작스럽게 결정됐지만
너네도 함께 해주면 좋겠어
I mean, we know it's short notice,
but we'd love you all to come with us.
내가 상상한 결혼식은
이게 아냐
No, no, no, this is not
the wedding I wanted!
드레스를 입고
I want to wear
my maid of honor dress
주목 받으며 입장하고 싶어
and walk down the aisle
with a hundred eyes on me,
현악 4중주는 'The Way You
Look Tonight'을 연주할 거야
while a string quartet plays
"The Way You Look Tonight."
우리가 고른 곡이 아닌데
That wasn't going to be
our processional music.
내가 골랐어
Well, it was going
to be mine!
초대해줘서 고맙지만
Thank you for the invitation,
but I have to decline
내가 즐길만한 게
아니니 거절할게
because it doesn't sound
like something I'll enjoy.
쉘든, 재밌을 거야
Come on, Sheldon,
it'll be fun.
영화 '그린 랜턴'에
대해서도 그렇게 말했잖아
That's what you said about
The Green Lantern movie.
114분 동안 틀렸더라
You were 114 minutes of wrong.
에이미는?
So, what do you say, Amy?
들러리 드레스 입어도 돼?
Can I wear my
maid of honor dress?
정말 시청까지 입고 가려고?
Seriously? You're going to
wear that thing to City Hall?
내 마지막 희망이야,
그것마저 뺏으려고?
It's all I have left! You're going
to take that from me, too?!
에이미, 이쁘다
Amy, you look great.
알아
I know.
맥주는 어디서 구했어?
Where'd you get a beer?
저기 문신을 잔뜩 한
커플이 줬어
From that happy young couple
over there
with all the tattoos.
너무 감동적이야,
라이벌 갱 소속인데
Beautiful story:
they're in rival drug gangs,
결혼하기로 했대
and they're getting married.
비밀이야
Shh, no one can know.
사랑에 빠진 사람들
사이에 있으니
Look at all these people
in love.
생각이 많아진다
It kind of gets you
thinking, doesn't it?
그러네
It does, indeed.
레너드
Leonard...
지금 여기 있는게 어색하지 않아?
is it awkward being here
with Penny given that
최근에 페니한테
프로포즈 했잖아
you recently
proposed to her?
프로포즈했어?
You proposed to Penny?
- 얘기하고 싶지 않아
- 어디서 했어?
I don't want to talk about it.
Where did he pop the question?
대답은?
What did you say?
거절 당했어
그만 얘기하자
She said, "No."
Can we drop it now?
진짜 프로포즈도 아니였어
It wasn't a real proposal.
왜 아니야?
Why wasn't it
a real proposal?
성교 도중에 물어봤거든
He asked her
during coitus.
한쪽 무릎 꿇었어?
아니면 원래 그런 자세였나?
Did you get down on one knee
or where you already there?
(chuckles)
오늘만은 자제해줘
Howard, don't talk like that
on your wedding day.
미안, 엄마
Sorry, Ma... Bernadette.
아니, 베르나데트
Ma... Burna...
You're ma Bernadette.
쉘튼한테 말했네,
잘하는 짓이다
Good move telling Sheldon.
프로포즈도 안 된다더니
이젠 친구랑 말도 못해?
What, I can't propose?
I can't talk to my friends?
또 하면 안 되는 거 있어?
Is there anything else
I'm not allowed to do?
그만해
All right,
that's enough.
너네 때문에
망치고 싶지 않아
Today is not
about you two.
하워드랑 베르나데트의 날이야
Today is about
Howard and Bernadette
그리고 나도 있지
and me.
여러분, 주목
Folks, can I have
your attention.
벌써 5시에요,
세 커플만 더 받을게요
It's 5:00, we're going to be
able to take three more couples.
나머지는 월요일에 계속하죠
The rest of you will have
to come back on Monday.
Oh, no.
걱정 마
I got this.
저기요
Excuse me?
저희는 오늘
꼭 해야되서요
But is there any way
you could squeeze us in?
사실 전 우주비행사인데
See, I'm an astronaut and
일요일에 러시아로 떠나서요
I'm leaving for Russia
on Sunday so
소유즈 로켓을 타고
국제우주정거장에 갑니다
I can take a Soyuz rocket to the
International Space Station.
네, 거기서 뵈요
Yeah, me, too.
I'll see you there.
결혼을 못 한다니
믿을 수 없어
I can't believe we're not
going to get married.
앞쪽에 혹시 들러리가
필요한지 물어보고 올게
Excuse me, I'm going
to go see if the couple
at the front of the line
needs a maid of honor.
그래서 집사람한테 말했지
DIMITRI:
So, I tell my wife,
개을 키우든 말든
난 산책 안 시킬 거야
"Get a dog, don't get a dog,
I'm not walking it,
먹이도 안 주고
똥도 안 치우고
I'm not feeding it,
I'm not picking up after it."
결국엔 네 몫이지
You know you're going
to wind up walking it.
알아
I know.
개 말고 우주 관련
얘기해야 되지 않아?
Uh, shouldn't you guys
be talking about
space stuff
instead of dogs?
디미트리
Dimitri,
우주 얘기를 해야
후르트룹스가 편한가봐
Froot Loops would be
more comfortable
if we talked about
space stuff.
그래
Okay,
난 우주로 나갈 거야
I'm going into space,
돌아오면 푸들 똥 치워야해
and when I come back,
I have to pick up a poodle crap.
나아졌어?
Is that better?
고마워
Thanks.
원한다면 베가스에서
결혼하는 것도 방법이지
You know, we could always drive
to Vegas and get married.
그건 너무 볼품 없잖아
No, it's that
kind of tacky?
베가스에서 결혼한
사람들 많이 아는데
Hey, I know tons of people
who got married in Vegas.
지금도 결혼한 상태야?
Are any of them
still married?
응, 파트너는 바뀌었지만
Yeah, I mean, not to
the same people but...
특별한 장소가
어딘가 있을 텐데
There's got to be some place
special we could do it.
레너드, 넌 페니랑
어디서 결혼하려고 했어?
Leonard, where did you
envision marrying Penny?
좀 닥칠래?
Will you shut up?
특별한 결혼식이 떠올랐어
Well, I know how to
make it special.
'사운드 오브 뮤직'에
나온 장면을 따라하기 싫다고
I told you we are not
recreating the wedding
from The Sound of Music.
응, 그건 잘 알아들었어
Yes, you made that
brutally clear to me.
일요일 아침까지
참을 수 있다면
What I was going to suggest is
if that you're willing to wait
구글 위성이 마침
패서디나를 지나갈 거야
until Sunday morning,
the Google satellite
will be over Pasadena.
우주에서 찍은
결혼식 사진이 남을 거야
You can have your wedding
photographed from space.
멋지다
PENNY: Oh...
That's so cool.
좋은 생각이야, 라지
Oh, wait to go, Raj.
I keep telling you,
내가 천체 물리학자가
아니였다면
if I wasn't an astrophysicist,
파티 플래너가 됐을 거야
I would have been
a party planner.
(laughs)
둘 중 하나였지
It was always a coin flip.
일요일 오전으로 결정됐고
Okay, so we know we're going
to do it Sunday morning.
이제 위성에서 잘
잡힐 장소를 찾아야해
Now we need to find a good place
for the satellite to see us.
우리 지붕은 어때?
How about our roof?
Oh, I like that.
That's great.
내 들러리 드레스가
구글 어스에 나오겠네
Oh, my gosh. I can't believe
my maid of honor dress
is going to be on Google Earth.
시간 장소를 정했으니
So, we have the
where and the when,
주례만 구하면 된다
but we still need to figure out
who's going to do the ceremony.
온라인에서 주례를
신청하면 돼
Well, that's easy.
Anyone can go online
and get ordained as a minister.
내가 아는 피어싱샵은
I know a piercing parlor,
where, for a hundred bucks,
$100에 주례를 서주고
they'll marry you
and stick a wedding ring
원하는 부위에
반지를 꼽아준대
through any body part you want.
누구로 하지?
Great, well,
who's it going to be?
내가 할게
SHELDON:
I'll do it,
클링곤으로 해도 된다면
provided I can perform
the ceremony in Klingon.
안돼
No.
대체 어디가
맘에 드는 거야?
What do you see in her?
(speaking Russian)
뭐가 샌다고?
Leaking? What's leaking?
연료
Fuel. Shh.
(man speaking Russian
over radio)
(speaking Russian)
연료가 새는데도 가는 거야?
There's fuel leaking
and we're still going to go?
정신줄 놓지마,
후르트룹스
Don't lose your Froot Loops,
Froot Loops.
자주 있는 일이야
This happens a lot.
90%는 문제 없어
Nine times out of ten,
no problem.
나머지 10%는?
What happens on the tenth time?
문제 있지
Problem.
얘들아
Hey, guys,
before I forget,
신랑 들러리
선물을 준비했어
I got you a little
groomsman present.
고마워,
뭘 이런 거까지
Oh, thanks, man.
You didn't have to do that.
판타스틱 4
1986년 3권
Fantastic Four,
annual number three from 1965,
민트급이지
in mint condition.
판타스틱과 인비져블이
결혼하는 내용이야
The one where Mr. Fantastic and
the Invisible Girl get married.
(chuckles) Oh, wow.
(chuckles)
이런
Oh, dear.
- 이럴까봐 두려웠어
- 뭐가?
I was afraid of this.
What?
이런 만화책이라면 최소
$100은 들었을 텐데
While a thoughtful gift, this
comic book in this condition
is worth at least
a hundred dollars.
그런데?
Yeah, so?
결혼 선물로 $88짜리
그레이비 그릇을 샀거든
I bought you an Bernadette
a gravy boat worth $88.
내가 너한테
빚을 진 거네
Which places me in your debt
그럴 수는 없어
and I can't be in your debt
언젠가 네가
이사를 도와달라거나
because someday you might
ask me to help you move...
살인을 시킬 수도 있잖아
...or to kill a man.
살인은 안 시킬걸
I doubt he'll ask you
to kill a man.
그게 유일한 해결책이라면?
Well, what if it's
his only way out?
위험을 감수하고 싶지 않아
I can't risk it.
$12 돌려줄게
Here is $12.
계산 끝났다
Now, we're even.
잠깐
(stammers) Wait...
카드도 샀어,
$2 돌려줘
I bought a card.
Give me two dollars.
선물이라면 질색이야
And for the record, this is why
I hate gift-giving.
누구세요?
AMY:
Who is it?
신랑입니다
It's the groom.
결혼식 전에
신부 보면 안돼
You can't come in.
Bad luck to see the bride.
Okay, uh, fine.
자기, 엄마가 데리러 오래
Bernie, I have to go
pick up my mother!
금방 갔다올게
I'll be right back!
왜 혼자 못 오셔?
BERNADETTE:
Why can't she drive herself?!
앉으면 드레스 망칠까봐
She doesn't want to sit in
her dress and wrinkle it
옆집 아저씨 밴에 눕히려고
so I'm going to lay her down in
the back of my neighbor's van!
알았어, 빨리와
All right, just hurry!
이따 봐, 엄마
Okay, I'll see you later,
Ma... uh...
아니, 아름다운 신부님
lovely bride-to-be.
조심해야겠다
I really got to watch that.
라지, 곧 시작한다
Come on, Raj,
we're ready to start.
내가 준비됐다고 해야
준비된 거야
What, we're ready,
when I say we're ready.
(muttering)
Ooh. (clears throat)
자, 이제 준비됐다
Okay, now we're ready.
엄마, 의자 여기로
옮겨 드릴까요?
Ma, you want to move your chair
over here so you can see?!
여기서 잘 보여
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I'm fine where I am!
지붕에서 떨어지기 싫어
I don't want to
fall off the roof!
떨어지기 전에
뚫고 내려가겠죠
You'll fall through the roof
before you fall off it.
페니
Penny.
(Vivaldi's Spring plays)
사돈이 볼만하네
Your new mother-in-law's
a piece of work.
나중에 말해요
Not now, Dad.
나보다 수염이 크잖아
She's got a
bigger mustache than me.
자, 여기
Here you go.
"Here you go"?
축구공 넘겨주는
것도 아니고
What am I, a football?
저 놈이 축구공을
잡을 리가 없지
Like that guy
could catch a football.
하워드와 베르나데트
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Howard and Bernadette,
우리 다섯 명이
주례를 보게 됐어
the five of us stand before you
as your friends
and newly ordained ministers.
더 크게
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Louder!
모두 주례를 봐 준대요
They all got ordained,
they're all marrying us,
근사하죠
it's adorable!
듣고 싶으면
가까이 오세요
If you want to hear it,
come closer!
너네 둘이 새로운 인생을
시작하는 걸 보면
Guys, when I look
at the two of you
starting your lives together,
it fills... my heart...
가슴이 벅차 올라
It fills my... heart...
(sobs)
시간이 좀 필요해
Okay, I'm going
to need a minute.
내가 먼저 할게
Okay, I'll, I'll go.
(clears throat)
하워드와 베르나데트
Howard and Bernadette,
I know you two
화려한 결혼식을
원했던 건 알지만
planned on getting married
in a big fancy wedding,
사랑에 빠졌을 때는
but when you're in love,
it doesn't matter where
장소나 순서가 중요하지 않아
or how these things happen.
곁에 누군가가
있다는게 중요하지
It just matters that
you have each other.
Hmm.
문제 있어?
Problem?
아니
No.
호프스태더 주례 선생님은
아이러니를 느끼겠지
I think the
Reverend Hofstadter
is making an
ironic connection
얼마 전 침실에서
프로포즈를 거절했잖아
between your statement about
love and your rejection
of his proposal
in the bedroom.
- 왜 이렇게 유치해?
- 난 아무 말 안했어
Oh, grow up.
Hey, I didn't say it.
그만 좀 해
All right, that's enough
from the both of you.
베르나데트,
들러리를 시켜줘서 고마워
Bernadette, I want to thank you
for allowing me to be
your maid of honor.
그리고 혹시라도
I also want you to know,
이번 결혼이 실패하면
다음에도 기꺼이 하겠어
that I will be happy
to do it again
if this marriage craps out.
고마워, 에이미
Thank you, Amy.
감동적이다
Very touching.
하워드와 베르나데트
Howard and Bernadette,
친구이자 연인인
둘은 축복받은 사이야
you are lucky enough to be best
friends who love each other.
제일 깊은 사랑이지
And that's the
strongest kind of love
배려, 인내와
존중으로 이뤄졌으니까
because at its core, it has
kindness, patience, and respect.
요즘에는 정말
찾기 어렵더라
Qualities that are hard to find
in people these days.
알로에 좀 줄까?
Would you like
some aloe vera?
좀 식혀야겠어
You just got burned.
내 차례다
All right, my turn.
(clears throat)
하워드, 베르나데트
Howard, Bernadette...
(speaking Klingon)
클링곤은 안 된다고 했지
Sheldon! I told
you no Klingon!
알았어, 영어로 할게
Fine, I'll do it in English,
그 느낌이 안 나지만
but it loses something.
다른 인간과 같이
살고 싶어하는 욕구는
The need to find another human
being to share one's life with,
나로서 이해하기 어려워
has always puzzled me.
내 자체가 너무나도
흥미로워서 말이야
Maybe because I'm so interesting
all by myself.
내가 내 자신에
만족하는 것처럼
With that being said,
may you find as much happiness
둘도 행복하길 바랄게
with each other
as I find on my own.
클링곤으로 하면
눈물 바다였을 텐데
The Klingon would have
made you cry.
결혼 서약은 준비했지?
I believe you two
have prepared vows?
하워드 조엘 왈로위츠
Howard Joel Wolowitz,
like you,
너와 비슷하게
짧지만 사랑스러운 서약이야
this is going to be
short and sweet.
진심으로 당신을 사랑하고
I love you with
all my heart and soul
영원히 그대 곁에
있기를 맹세합니다
and promise
to be with you forever.
베르나데트 매리앤
로스텐코우스키
Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski...
안 들려
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Speak up!
저한테 소리지를 권리는
이 여자만이 갖고 있어요
Hey, from now on, she's the
only women who can yell at me!
당신을 만나기 전에
Until I met you,
한 명의 여자와 남은 인생을
보내는 건 상상도 못했는데
I couldn't imagine spending
my life with just one person...
(chuckles)
이제는 당신 없이
...and now I can't imagine
하루도 못 보낼 것 같습니다
spending one day
of it without you.
캘리포니아 주에 의해
저희에게 주어진 권위로
ALL:
By the power vested in us,
by the state of California...
클링곤 최고의회도
and the Klingon High Council...
둘을 부부로 선언합니다
...we now pronounce you husband
and wife.
(all cheering)
발사된다
That's ignition.
이 부분이 제일 좋아
I love this part!
나도
Me, too!
만감이 교차하네
I have strongly mixed feelings!
드디어 가는구나
Oh, my God,
it's happening.
놓쳤어?
Did I miss it?
아직, 빨리와
No, come on in. Hurry.
(rocket engine rumbling on TV)
내가 사랑하는 남자야
I love that man.
나도
Me, too.
믿을 수 없어
I can't believe it.
지금까지 뻥인 줄 알았거든
This whole time, a small part
of me thought he was lying.
(man speaking in Russian
over TV)
자, 시작이야
This is it.
용감히 떠나라, 하워드
Boldly go,
Howard Wolowitz.
(man speaking Russian over TV)
WOLOWITZ:
Oy vay...!
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com